{"items": [{"question": "boot-licking", "answer": "obsequious", "options": ["obsequies", "obstreperous", "querulous", "obsequious"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "funeral ceremonies or traditions", "answer": "obsequies", "options": ["obstreperous", "supercilious", "querulous", "obsequies"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "noisy and difficult to control", "answer": "obstreperous", "options": ["querulous", "impecunious", "supercilious", "obstreperous"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "Habitually complaining", "answer": "querulous", "options": ["indigent", "impecunious", "supercilious", "querulous"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "Expressive of contempt", "answer": "supercilious", "options": ["supercilious", "pecuniary", "indigent", "impecunious"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "Not having enough money to pay for necessities", "answer": "impecunious", "options": ["destitute", "pecuniary", "impecunious", "indigent"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "who is very poor", "answer": "indigent", "options": ["chivalry", "destitute", "indigent", "pecuniary"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "Relating to or involving money", "answer": "pecuniary", "options": ["pecuniary", "chivalry", "chivalrous", "destitute"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "lacking food, clothing and shelter", "answer": "destitute", "options": ["chivalrous", "destitute", "chivalry", "cavalry"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "Courtesy towards women", "answer": "chivalry", "options": ["chivalrous", "cavalry", "cavalier", "chivalry"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "Being attentive to women like an ideal knight", "answer": "chivalrous", "options": ["cavalcade", "cavalier", "cavalry", "chivalrous"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "a group of soldiers", "answer": "cavalry", "options": ["cavalcade", "cavalier", "noxious", "cavalry"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "Not caring enough about something important", "answer": "cavalier", "options": ["cavalier", "cavalcade", "innocuous", "noxious"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "a line of riders or carriages moving together", "answer": "cavalcade", "options": ["bib", "noxious", "innocuous", "cavalcade"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "Injurious to physical or mental health", "answer": "noxious", "options": ["bibulous", "noxious", "innocuous", "bib"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "Not injurious to physical or mental health", "answer": "innocuous", "options": ["bibulous", "bib", "imbibe", "innocuous"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "Top part of an apron; covering the chest", "answer": "bib", "options": ["imbibe", "bibulous", "cadaver", "bib"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "addicted to or fond of alcoholic beverages", "answer": "bibulous", "options": ["cadaverous", "imbibe", "bibulous", "cadaver"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "to take in", "answer": "imbibe", "options": ["cadaverous", "decadent", "cadaver", "imbibe"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "The dead body of a human being", "answer": "cadaver", "options": ["cadaver", "decadent", "cadaverous", "dolour"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "Very thin especially from disease, hunger or cold", "answer": "cadaverous", "options": ["cadaverous", "dolour", "doleful", "decadent"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "Being in a state of decline or decay", "answer": "decadent", "options": ["condole", "decadent", "dolour", "doleful"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "(poetry) painful grief", "answer": "dolour", "options": ["obsequious", "condole", "dolour", "doleful"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "Filled with or evoking sadness", "answer": "doleful", "options": ["obsequies", "obsequious", "doleful", "condole"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "Express one's sympathetic grief, on the occasion of someone's death", "answer": "condole", "options": ["obsequies", "obstreperous", "condole", "obsequious"], "answer_index": 3}], "title": "Word power Made Easy - Session 45.txt", "total": 25}